Anh T. Nguyen

Ç teeann | ⊕ teeann.github.io | ≥ Anh T Nguyen | ≥ nguyentheanh2903@gmail.com |

OVERVIEW

I am a Research Resident in Machine Learning at VinAI Research. My research focus has primarily been on domain adaptation with applications to computer vision. Broadly speaking, my focus lies in developing machine learning models capable of adapting and generalizing efficiently across diverse domains, enhancing their practical applicability in real-world scenarios.

EDUCATION

2016 - 2021 B.Sc in Computer Science at Hanoi University of Science and Technology

GPA: 3.63/4.0, Top: 1%, graduated with Excellent Degree.

Thesis: A Variational Information Bottleneck Method for Network Intrusion Detection.

EXPERIENCE

AI Resident Mar 2022 - present

- Research topics: Domain Adaptation, Domain Generalization

- Conducted research on domain generalization and domain adaptation with generalized target shift.

Security Researcher

Sep 2018 - Dec 2019

- Conducted web penetration testing for enterprise clients
- Developed vulnerability scanning plugins for web application security scanner.
- Discovered security vulnerabilities CVE-2019-13488, CVE-2019-13489 and CVE-2019-11449 in open-source software.

Submissions

Anh, Nguyen The, T. T. Lam, et al. (2023). "Conditional Support Alignment for Domain Adaptation with Label Shift". In: *Under review at ICLR24*, scores 6-6-5. URL: https://openreview.net/forum?id=FJjHQS2DyE.

Publications

Anh, Nguyen The, V. D. Minh, T. H. Hai, et al. (2021). "BKIDset-A New Intrusion Detection Dataset To Mitigate The Class Imbalance Problem". In: 2021 15th International Conference on Advanced Computing and Applications (ACOMP). IEEE, pp. 106–111.

Thieu, V. V., **Anh, Nguyen The**, and T. H. Hai (2022). "A Variational Information Bottleneck Method for Network Intrusion Detection". In: *Journal of Communications*. Vol. 17, pp. 933–940.

Honors and Awards

- Erasmus+ scholarship for exchange study at Uppsala University
- Consolation Prize at ASEAN Student Contest on Information Security Final 2019
- Third Prize at Regional Round of ASEAN Student Contest on Information Security 2019
- Top 20 students with highest scores at 2016 Vietnam National University Entrance Exam

- Silver medal at Asia-Pacific Mathematical Olympiad for Primary Schools 2010 (APMOPS)
- **Discovered** security vulnerabilities CVE-2019-13488, CVE-2019-13489 and CVE-2019-11449 in open-source software.

LANGUAGES

• Vietnamese: native

• English: IELTS Overall 8.0: 8.5 R, 9.0 L, 7.0 W, 7.0 S

TECHNICAL SKILLS

• DevOps: Linux, Docker

• **Programming:** Python, Java, C/C++

• Libraries: Pytorch, TensorFlow, NumPy, etc.